=Wow The World S2=
(Recap Special)
(Variety show OG's highlight moments)
(Wants to explain
but doesn't know what to say)
Not loud enough, shout again.
Like in those xianxia dramas.
Scream at the sky.
Right.
(Furiously wiping his hands)
(Shout)
(Pressured)
(Go all out)
Ah!
(Can't look down)
(Observing)
There are
all kinds of people.
Take off your jacket
and put it on Chen He.
Take off your jacket.
Put it on...
Put it on him.
I think you're a bit cold.
(Choking with emotion)
(Trying)
(Giving up)
(Rushing)
Take off your jacket and put it on him.
Take off your jacket
and put it on Chen He.
(Sweating)
Let me guess.
Someone is controlling you, right?
(Already seen through)
He's guessed it.
(Variety show OG's intuition)
(Looking sideways)
No.
No?
Seems like your brain is in your ears.
Now.
(Weakly)
No.
I think
the person controlling you
lacks creativity
so far.
It's average.
(Sharp comment)
Nothing special.
Go over and kiss him.
(Creative enough now?)
Go hug him.
The ones
who arrived earlier, right?
Take off your coat.
Put it on him.
Take off your coat and put it on him.
(Call connected)
No.
Why are you talking to yourself?
(Super cooperative)
Wait, let's dance.
No.
Isn't this the monitor?
Is this machine the monitor?
(Seen through again)
How did I not notice?
No.
I'm speechless.
Oh, no.
(The variety show rookie
is completely shaken)
Oh, no.
Xingxu, give the earpiece to He.
Wait.
(Instant answer)
Someone wants to talk to you.
He's reacting pretty fast now.
He.
Honglei.
(Well-behaved)
Alright.
Once you know he's got an earpiece in,
it's no fun anymore.
(On the phone)
Right.
You need to switch to someone else.
(Outsider)
It doesn't even matter
if I have an earpiece or not.
(Facing reality)
Alright.
I'll leave you two to it.
(Free communication)
Come on, let's do it normally.
Why did you come on this variety show?
Wait.
How did the tables turn?
No.
Honglei, no.
The tables have turned.
Someone just asked me a question.
He asked me,
"Do you think you are
more handsome or Honglei is?"
What do you think?
(Dead inside)
But honestly, He.
Honglei.
Who is more handsome, you or me?
Honglei,
in the previous shows,
you had the title Visual King.
My nickname was
Visual Devil.
(Can't get a word in)
How about this?
Anyway,
this is the first episode,
right?
Let's put it to a vote online
and see it through to the end.
(Unexpected battle)
Okay.
I accept the challenge.
How about this?
Let's add Li Naiwen in.
Let him serve as the foil.
Hahaha.
You know, Naiwen said
(Helping him get familiar with others)
he didn't and wouldn't do
variety shows.
Now,
he's been on all the variety shows.
He is too scary.
(Wants to speak
but doesn't know what to say)
(Encouragement)
Are you not going to talk
once you don't have the earpiece?
A more introverted person
needs to build
more familiarity with everyone.
(Leaves first)
So the more introverted one, Xingxu,
stays behind.
What did he say?
Chen He left.
Xingxu's left here again.
(Only him getting hurt)
Honglei.
You guessed it.
Yes, he's so obvious.
Sit.
Come.
Liu Yuning.
You're so tall.
How are you so tall?
(Sitting down to lower blood pressure)
You come.
You direct.
(New connection established)
Xingxu, later...
When I came just now,
I instantly found
you were being controlled.
You have to
be absolutely flawless.
Let's go.
How much money do you have left?
I haven't spent any money.
How about I follow you
and you
treat me to something to eat?
Go.
Let's go together.
You go take a walk.
(I'll feed first)
You take a walk.
Go take a walk.
(You're next)
(Not yet)
Do you know why I sent Li Naiwen away?
(He did it on purpose)
Why?
Being with him never ends well.
He has too many tricks.
And his face.
I tell you.
Why?
I don't know why.
(Staff)
He has a role in every activity.
We can find a place to sit down,
or whatever.
Let's grab some coffee.
Grab some coffee.
You weren't here a few days ago.
I was going
to let you lead me
in some exercise every day.
(Step 1: Trigger keyword "exercise")
Exercise.
I'll do it.
Okay.
Hello.
I want some coffee.
(A hint of coldness
and a touch of nonchalance)
It's the espresso.
Espresso.
Okay.
(A wicked smile)
Sit.
(Serious)
Then what?
What did you say?
(Step 2: Lead Chili into the topic)
Lead me in exercise.
But you weren't there.
No.
So I binge-ate for several days.
I mainly...
I...
(In a very low voice)
Touch me.
(Ready for relay)
(Everything under control)
(Step 3: Play hard to get)
You showed me the photos.
You're jacked.
You seem to have no body fat at all.
I do have body fat.
But I only have five-pack abs.
Only five-pack abs.
Abs are innate.
The number is determined by genes.
(Wanna touch them?)
The symmetry is determined by genes too.
Gong Jun's are very symmetrical.
(Owner of a six-pack)
Gong Jun has six, very symmetrical.
There's nothing you can do about it.
A matter of talent.
I've never gotten to touch...
(Step 4: From "exercise" to "touch")
Gotten to touch...
Gotten to touch
my own abs.
I hope you can lead me
and let me touch them once.
(Without a doubt)
No problem, absolutely.
(Naturally)
What he's looking at is
(Pinch)
this place.
(Happiness suddenly arrives)
(Pinch x2)
This place.
(Step 5: A game of cat and mouse; Let go)
Absolutely no body fat.
(Why did you let go?
Opportunity knocks but once)
(One more to go, what to do?)
(Actively luring)
Look here.
Touch here.
(Pinch x3)
(Successful relay)
(I did it)
(I did it too)
Your muscles are rock hard.
And here.
Here.
You touch from top to bottom.
(Keep acting, we're both professionals)
Touch from top to bottom.
You can feel the cut.
How do you train this?
Don't think of it as a burden.
Just train whatever you want.
If I were like him,
I would never wear clothes outside.
I would never wear any.
Lend me some later.
(Take all you want)
No, I mean...
All of it?
That's not necessary.
After you pay, give me 20.
(No Chili Way)
(Chen He plays a good person)
No, after I pay, you use it.
(Chen Xingxu plays a good person)
All for me?
All for you.
(Xingxu, you make me feel guilty)
(He, take it as my apology)
I vouch for him.
(Clearing him as good)
The basic logic of this game is
not being afraid to spend the money.
He doesn't want clues.
He doesn't want clues at all.
So he's definitely a good person.
(Suppressing a smile)
Well.
Whatever role, it's not important.
Let's finish eating first.
Now I think
you should be careful.
Be careful of Li Naiwen.
I guess it's Yuning.
Yuning is smart.
Jun is slyly bad.
Why haven't you suspected me at all?
(What do you think?)
You're okay.
You're new here.
No need to put so much pressure on you.
(Both breathed a sigh of relief)
Let's go.
Let's go buy something.
I'll walk over there.
Okay, I'll go this way.
Okay.
(Successfully fed the kill)
I've completed the mission.
(It's in the bag)
I didn't...
start it.
I also paid
for it.
I gave him
money.
So my conscience is clear.
He is a really good person.
(A good role makes the actor)
Good person.
Given Xingxu's level,
if I didn't go up and sacrifice myself,
today would end.
He thinks he was amazing
and flawless.
(Chen He's letting loose moment)
Of course.
Don't exercise, okay?
He's been exercising next to me.
Of course.
Wait.
Your hearing is too good.
He is totally immersed in it.
He has total conviction.
Say "of course"
in ten languages.
Of course.
Why do I feel like I can do it now?
(Confidence regained)
Let's duel.
(I won't go easy on you)
Come on.
Honglei, I'll duel with him.
This is a personal grudge.
Personal grudge.
He thinks he can do it.
(Li Naiwen vs. Chen He
purely personal grudge)
Of course.
Very confident.
You want me to say it,
or you say it?
Naiwen.
Of everyone I've met,
you're the cutest.
(Eye-opening)
(Philtrum control)
(Twitching)
Hold it in.
(Full-on attack)
(Total collapse)
(In the name of the moon, I'll punish you)
Seven characters.
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
What?
What, what?
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
(Lost again)
What is this thing?
That's spot on. He did the move.
(Current score 4:6)
This is very accurate.
(Trying hard to connect)
Anything related to animation
is fine by me.
(It's in He's wheelhouse)
I don't know how to dance this.
Me neither.
You think I can?
(It hasn't been updated in my playlist)
Ah, socks.
(Sliced beef offal in chili sauce)
[*Literally means couple's lung slices]
Four characters.
(Sliced beef offal in chili sauce)
Childhood sweethearts?
Sworn friends.
Bosom buddies.
Like this.
Loving each other.
Heart to heart.
(Watch closely)
Heart.
(Xin, xin, xin, xin, xin)
Here.
I think we two need to be more obvious.
We will be.
Just like this.
Four characters.
Like this.
Enter the room.
Newlywed cere...
- Newlyweds.
(Is this a couple's...?)
Heart.
(Expectant)
Worried sick.
(Guessing blindly)
Dear heart.
Filthy rich.
Stop fighting, you guys.
(What is this?)
Giving birth.
Let's calm down.
Let's all calm down, okay?
Calm down, take it slow.
(Calm down)
Heartbroken.
(I can't calm down)
Kidneys? Related to kidneys?
Sizzling pork kidney.
(Look at this)
(Lung, lung)
Take a knife for a friend.
Wait.
Wait, I'll show you.
(Never give up)
Wait.
(Gong Jun's sliced beef offal in chili sauce:
1. Slice the lung)
(2. Sprinkle on the sauce)
Rip out one's heart and lungs.
Rip out one's heart.
Let's think about it.
You got one right.
I'll give you a hint.
Look, you got one character right.
It's starting.
Eat.
You got one character right.
- "Heart" is correct.
Right.
(I can only laugh)
(Making things worse)
Heart and hand connected.
(What on earth is it?)
Rip out one's heart.
This is too hard.
(Have mercy)
Pass.
(Keep working on it)
No pass.
Again.
Just this one.
(I'm hyped, even though I don't get it)
No changing, right?
No changing.
Okay, no changing.
Then change the song.
Wait, I'll get a prop.
Be careful with that.
Be careful.
Wedding ring.
Marriage.
Cowherd and Weaver Girl.
(My fists are clenched)
I don't care anymore.
I'm taking all of you down with me.
(Starting to pray for rain)
Is this related to the topic, bro?
(Drop a bomb)
Bro.
(Destroy)
(Bury the question)
(Off you go)
(He was doing fine)
(The little plane is here)
(Can't understand at all)
What?
He's gone crazy.
Don't listen to him.
I'll give you the final hint.
(Domain expansion)
Eager to return.
Getting close. Go on.
On a whim.
Very close.
(Think fast)
Not close!
He's messing with you.
Stop guessing.
(Drop another bomb)
He's messing around.
(Sprinkling black pepper)
Don't look at him.
It's okay. Jun, you go on.
Eat the heart.
Spicy heart, ruthless.
Eat spicy food.
Heart in bloom.
(Only thinking about "heart")
I've guessed almost every "heart" word.
(Really need to stop him)
Give a hint.
Food.
(Braised duck, sauced duck, cured meat,
sliced beef offal in chili sauce)
(Pheasant, canned quail,
flower-shaped shark fin, pickled meat)
(Steamed sea bass, fried noodles,
glazed pork knuckle, white meat)
Sliced beef offal in chili sauce.
Awesome, you win.
(Situations He can't control)
(Clip from the drama Flowers in Fog)
I kissed you.
But it was a compliment to you.
I want you to pay
for that slap.
I want to complete my compliment to you.
I completed my compliment to you.
Just a polite good night to you.
You.
Little bro.
Everything that happens next
will be very disgusting.
Is it as disgusting as that?
Yes.
Listen to me carefully.
You are a girl now.
I kissed you downstairs.
But it was a compliment to you.
I want you to pay
for that slap.
(Pay how?)
I want to complete my compliment to you.
(Chen He)
There's more?
I completed my compliment to you.
Just a polite good night
to you.
(Circle-Covering Dance, Round 2)
Okay.
You started it.
So ugly.
What kind of dance is this?
It doesn't matter.
A real man cares about his face.
My heart hurts so much.
Lin Yi.
What are you doing, Lin Yi?
Lin Yi, are you itchy?
Go take a shower, Lin Yi.
(Wriggling around)
Come on.
Okay, I'll give them a move.
Go easy on me.
What is this move?
(Face in danger)
Good.
Great.
What's the move?
What do we do now?
How do I do this?
What should we do?
Turn around.
It's dangerous.
Do I cover it?
Well.
Wait.
My chest.
What's wrong with your chest?
I need someone to cover my chest.
Okay, come on.
(Struggling to move)
(Eyes full of determination)
(Back ramrod straight)
(Taking a horse stance)
Look at Lin Yi.
It's tough for Yi.
Put your palms together
and shake your head.
Clap your hands and shake your head.
(Lending a leg)
Shake your head.
From top to bottom.
Alright.
Okay.
So close.
That's enough.
Second person.
Is this okay?
It's okay.
Then...
(Touch)
(Isn't this a bit too much?)
What are you touching?
(A hardworking little hand)
Come on.
Right, head this way first.
One, two, three.
What kind of performance art is this?
Come on.
Lin Yi.
(Chest exposed)
Lin Yi, come.
Naiwen, cover your chest.
Naiwen.
(Lost in right-hand conducting)
Naiwen, your chest.
I forgot.
Come on.
It's most likely with He.
He's the only one covering
his face with his right hand,
so it's more convenient.
(Successfully drawing fire)
Most likely in He's right hand.
Right.
Face.
He almost gave me a big slap.
Okay.
(Moving away smoothly)
Lin Yi's pecs are so bouncy.
(Can't help but praise,
forgets to cover his chest)
(The only two trying)
You're not covering mine anymore?
What is he doing?
He went to chat.
Okay.
You don't have to
cover the chest anymore.
Eliminated.
(Emergency fix)
You cover the wrong place.
You got left and right wrong.
It's okay.
No chest covering. We're freer.
(Completely abandons the chest cover)
This hand is free.
(Locking onto everyone's faces)
Definitely on their faces.
Right.
The second move is this.
Okay, just like this, come on.
Okay.
(Nai takes the initiative)
(But it's unnecessary)
Naiwen.
His left face has never been covered.
Why are you covering it?
No.
Confusion.
Mislead.
Who can you mislead?
For a sense of involvement.
A sense of involvement.
(Sun Honglei)
(Busy hands)
Exposed.
(Flustered feet)
(Accidentally)
(Completely unaware)
Lin Yi, your face.
Your face.
Your own face.
(Whole body completely exposed)
(Ahhhhhh)
(Ho ho ho ho)
It's a total failure.
(Forgetful Naiwen, unhelpful Yi)
(Speechless He)
(Clenched fists)
Now there are only two options.
It's obvious.
We...
We're too stupid.
I give up.
Two idiots.
Quick.
Come cover my face.
I'll leave you two to it.
Hurry up.
It's on my face.
(Owning his handsome look)
Lin Yi isn't covering himself anymore.
He is not hiding anymore.
This cracks me up.
Lin Yi, you're our treasure.
I can see it.
Bow down and admit guilt.
Okay.
Come on, one more move.
What is all this?
Alright, awesome.
Go on, flip your hair.
Come on, it's simple.
(Sticking to his post)
That.
You don't need to cover it anymore.
Go away, Lin Yi.
Lin Yi, no need to cover.
(Listens to everyone)
He really walked away.
(Standing obediently)
Lin Yi, come here.
(Standing still)
Lin Yi.
Cover this side tightly.
He really can't help with anything.
Ready, go.
It could also be...
It could also be on Naiwen.
Impossible.
Really?
Chen He.
Look.
He didn't even say left or right first.
He's too casual.
He's too relaxed.
(Firmly guessing Chen He)
It's on He.
Okay.
Come on.
(An unnecessary palm)
Is this necessary?
Lin Yi, just do it freely.
You can just do it freely.
Alright.
Bow down and admit guilt.
You two are really something.
My bad.
They both forgot.
They got carried away
and turned the match
into pure fun.
Come on, please state your answer.
(Choose Li Naiwen)
Li Naiwen.
(Choose Chen He)
He.
You guys really...
Just two people.
Exactly.
(The circle is here)
=Wow The World S2=